const artQuestions = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "Which two primary colors combine to create Green?",
    choices: [
      "Red and Yellow",
      "Blue and Yellow",
      "Black and Yellow",
      "Blue and Red",
    ],
    answer: "Blue and Yellow",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "Artist known for his abstract, colorful drip paintings?",
    choices: ["Pablo Picasso", "Claude Monet", "Jackson Pollock", "Mark Steve"],
    answer: "Jackson Pollock",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "What is the main difference between Serif and Sans-Serif font?",
    choices: [
      "Serif fonts have small decorative lines at the end of letter strokes, while Sans-Serif fonts do not.",
      "Serif fonts are older fonts",
      "Serif fonts are bolded.",
      "Serif fonts are used in headlines.",
    ],
    answer:
      "Serif fonts have small decorative lines at the end of letter strokes, while Sans-Serif fonts do not.",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question:
      "What is the term for an empty space around objects and text in design?",
    choices: [
      "Positive Space",
      "Texture",
      "Focal Point",
      "White/Negative Space",
    ],
    answer: "White/Negative Space",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question:
      "Which Skyscraper was the world's tallest for nearly 40 years after 1931?",
    choices: [
      "Burj Khalifa",
      "Wills Tower",
      "Empire State Building",
      "Chrysler Building",
    ],
    answer: "Empire State Building",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question:
      "What term describes a designer using only two fonts that complement each other?",
    choices: ["Kerning", "Leading", "Tracking", "Font Pairing"],
    answer: "Font Pairing",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question:
      "What is the principle that suggests elements close together are perceived as belonging to the same group?",
    choices: [
      "Principle of Proximity",
      "Alignment",
      "Repetition",
      "Proximity of Scale",
    ],
    answer: "Principle of Proximity",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "What is the main purpose of a website's wireframe?",
    choices: [
      "Defining the final color scheme",
      "Laying out the structure and content hierarchy",
      "Writing the website content",
      "Testing the code functionality",
    ],
    answer: "Laying out the structure and content hierarchy",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question:
      "When designing a logo, a designer typically creates two primary versions: Vertical and ____ ?",
    choices: ["Bold", "Horizontal", "Flat", "Simplified"],
    answer: "Horizontal",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question:
      "Which color system is primarily used for dispaying images on digital screens (monitors, phones)?",
    choices: ["CMYK", "RGB", "Pantone", "HEX"],
    answer: "RGB",
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    question: " The Colosseum is located in which city?",
    choices: ["Athens", "Cairo", "Rome", "Instabul"],
    answer: "Rome",
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    question: 'A website is considered "Responsive" when it ____',
    choices: [
      "Only uses high-resolution images",
      "Loads quickly on all networks",
      "Adjust its layout and content to fit different screen sizes",
      "Has a high level of security",
    ],
    answer: "Adjust its layout and content to fit different screen sizes",
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    question: "Who sculpted the bronze of Perseus with the Head of Medusa?",
    choices: [
      "Leonardo da Vinci",
      "Benvenuto Cellini",
      "Michelangelo",
      "Donatello",
    ],
    answer: "Benvenuto Cellini",
  },
];

export default artQuestions;
